let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "The number of edges from root to the node is called ",
        answer: "Depth",
        options: [
          "Height", 
          "Depth",
          "Length",
          "Width"
        ]
      },{
        numb:2,
        question: "The no of external nodes in a full binary tree with n internal nodes is?",
        answer: "n+1",
        options: [
          "n",
          "n+1",
          "2n",
          "2n + 1"
         
        ]
      },{
        numb: 3,
        question: "A Binary Tree can have",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
          "Can have 2 children",
          "Can have 1 children",
          "Can have 0 children",
          "All of the above"
          
        ]
      },{
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following is a true about Binary Trees?",
        answer: "None of the above",
        options: [
          "Every complete binary tree is also a full binary tree.",
          "Every full binary tree is also a complete binary tree.",
          "No binary tree is both complete and full.",
          "None of the above"
          
        ]
      },{
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following is not an advantage of trees?",
        answer: "Undo/Redo operations in a notepad",
        options: [
          "Hierarchical structure",
          "Faster search",
          "Router algorithms",
          "Undo/Redo operations in a notepad"
        ]
      },{
        numb: 6,
        question: "The difference between the external path length and the internal path length of a binary tree with n internal nodes is?",
        answer: "2n",
        options: [
          "1",
          "n",
          "n + 1",
          "2n"
        ]
      },{
        numb: 7,
        question: "If the tree is not a complete binary tree then what changes can be made for easy access of children of a node in the array ?",
        answer: "every node stores data saying which of its children exist in the array",
        options: [
          "every node stores data saying which of its children exist in the array",
          "no need of any changes continue with 2w and 2w+1, if node is at i",
          "keep a seperate table telling children of a node",
          "use another array parallel to the array with tree"
        ]
      },{
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the time complexity of level order traversal?",
        answer: "O(n)",
        options: [
          "O(1)",
          "O(n)",
          "O(logn)",
          "O(nlogn)"
          ]
      },{
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the average case time complexity for finding the height of the binary tree?",
        answer: "h = O(log n)",
        options: [
          "h = O(loglogn)",
          "h = O(nlogn)",
          "h = O(n)",
          "h = O(log n)"
        ]
      },{
        numb: 10,
        question: "In a full binary tree if there are L leaves, then total number of nodes N are?",
        answer: "N = 2*L - 1",
        options: [
          "N = 2*L",
          "N = L + 1",
          "N = L - 1",
          "N = 2*L - 1"
        ]
      },
    ];